<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>rhysmg</title>
    
    
    <description>rhysmg - I'm not sure this makes sense...</description>
    
    <link>http://mgmt:4000/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://mgmt:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Trust me</title>
        <description>
          
          Originally posted to Facebook: Folks, I need to put a few things straight and make some apologies. A couple of days ago, I posted (to Facebook, not my blog post from the 19th) about my opposition to vaccine mandates and my support to those who are peacefully protesting. When I...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 23 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>http://mgmt:4000/2022-02-23-trust_me/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mgmt:4000/2022-02-23-trust_me/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>You don't owe me your body</title>
        <description>
          Informed consent – hard won, now lost? - 
          Kia Ora whānau Aotearoa. After countless sleepless nights and the shedding of tears as I’ve seen my country, my beautiful Aotearoa New Zeeland torn and hurting, I feel compelled once again by my convictions to write to you in aroha and fervour. I want to address the question at the...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 19 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>http://mgmt:4000/2022-02-19-you_dont_owe_me_your_body/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mgmt:4000/2022-02-19-you_dont_owe_me_your_body/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sample blog post</title>
        <description>
          Each post also has a subtitle - 
          This is a demo post to show you how to write blog posts with markdown. I strongly encourage you to take 5 minutes to learn how to write in markdown - it’ll teach you how to transform regular text into bold/italics/headings/tables/etc. Here is some bold text Here is a secondary...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 28 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>http://mgmt:4000/2020-02-28-test-markdown-copy/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mgmt:4000/2020-02-28-test-markdown-copy/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Flake it till you make it</title>
        <description>
          Excerpt from Soulshaping by Jeff Brown - 
          Under what circumstances should we step off a path? When is it essential that we finish what we start? If I bought a bag of peanuts and had an allergic reaction, no one would fault me if I threw it out. If I ended a relationship with a woman who...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 26 Feb 2020 00:00:00 +1300</pubDate>
        <link>http://mgmt:4000/2020-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://mgmt:4000/2020-02-26-flake-it-till-you-make-it/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
